let questions = [
    {
        question: "The manager that was SACKED last month has been: ________",
        answer: "C. reinstated",
        options: [
            "A. retired",
            "B. sober",
            "C. reinstated",
            "D. promoted"
        ]
    },
    {
      question: "Words spoken in the heat of the argument could OFFEND rather than _______________",
      answer: "A. pacify",
      options: [
          "A. pacify",
          "B. amuse",
          "C. inspire",
          "D. irritate"
      ]
  },
  {
    question: "Some OUTSPOKE social critics live a _________ life.",
    answer: "A. reserved",
    options: [
        "A. reserved",
        "B. happy",
        "C. boisterous",
        "D. still"
    ]
},
{
  question: "The testimony was VAGUE and void of __________ details.",
  answer: "A. specific",
  options: [
      "A. specific",
      "B. minute",
      "C. transparent",
      "D. hidden"
  ]
},
{
  question: "John is consistentLY ASSERTIVE whereas his brother is _____________",
  answer: "C. reserved",
  options: [
      "A. cautious",
      "B. cowardly",
      "C. reserved",
      "D. respectful"
  ]
},
{
  question: "He is quite an OUTSPOKEN man, but his father is _____________",
  answer: "C. taciturn ",
  options: [
      "A. humorous",
      "B. sober",
      "C. taciturn",
      "D. silent"
  ]
},
{
  question: "Personally, I GIVE IN when it comes to arguments, but Benjamin often __________ his opinion.",
  answer: "B. holds on",
  options: [
      "A. holds in",
      "B. holds on",
      "C. holds back",
      "D. holds up"
  ]
},
{
  question: "The policies of the government favor the ELITE rather than the _________",
  answer: "A. masses",
  options: [
      "A. masses",
      "B. oppressed",
      "C. public",
      "D. unemployed"
  ]
},
{
  question: "The policies of the government favor the ELITE rather than the _________",
  answer: "A. masses",
  options: [
      "A. masses",
      "B. oppressed",
      "C. public",
      "D. unemployed"
  ]
},
{
  question: "Through hardwork, Precious OUTSHONE her colleague rather than being ___________",
  answer: "A. overshadowed",
  options: [
      "A. overshadowed",
      "B. demoted",
      "C. defeated",
      "D. submerged"
  ]
},
{
  question: "Though the position of minister was CONFERRED on him, it was ________ due to his dishonesty.",
  answer: "C. revoked",
  options: [
      "A. reversed",
      "B. recalled",
      "C. revoked",
      "D. reclaimed"
  ]
},
{
  question: "The government's effort to IMPROVE the economy rather _________ it.",
  answer: "D. worsened",
  options: [
      "A. destroyed",
      "B. complicated",
      "C. spoilt",
      "D. worsened"
  ]
},
{
  question: "Despite all my attempt to REFUTE all the charges against me, my sister tried to __________ them",
  answer: "D. maintain",
  options: [
      "A. defend",
      "B. prove",
      "C. investigate",
      "D. maintain"
  ]
},
{
  question: "Good teaching STIMULATES the interest of the students whereas bad teaching _____________ it.",
  answer: "A. dampens",
  options: [
      "A. dampens",
      "B. encourages",
      "C. supersedes",
      "D. retracts"
  ]
},
{
  question: "The purpose of education is to ENHANCE progress and not _________ it.",
  answer: "C. impede",
  options: [
      "A. proscribe",
      "B. intercept",
      "C. impede",
      "D. confuse"
  ]
},

{
  question: "The investigators relied solely on CONJECTURES rather than ________.",
  answer: "A. facts",
  options: [
      "A. facts",
      "B. hearsays",
      "C. figures",
      "D. fabrications"
  ]
},
{
  question: "The man was accused of PREMEDITATED murder but he proved it was ____________.",
  answer: "B. accidental",
  options: [
      "A. determined",
      "B. accidental",
      "C. planned",
      "D. contrived"
  ]
},
{
  question: "The HANDSOME amount from her business differs from the _________ returns from her husband's business.",
  answer: "B. meagre",
  options: [
      "A. ugly",
      "B. meagre",
      "C. modest",
      "D. lowly"
  ]
},
{
  question: "The officer was expecting to be __________; unfortunately, he was CENSURED",
  answer: "B. praised",
  options: [
      "A. questioned",
      "B. praised",
      "C. decorated",
      "D. guided"
  ]
},
    {
        question: "We tend to dislike it when activities are MONOTONOUS",
        answer: "A. varied",
        options: [
            "A. varied",
            "B. alike",
            "C. miserable",
            "D. natural"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Uthman Danfodio lived AN ASCETIC life.",
        answer: "A. a pleasurabe/hedonist/epicurean/self-indulging",
        options: [
            "A. a pleasurabe/hedonist/epicurean/self-indulging",
            "B. an austere/pleasruable/secular",
            "C. a flamboyant/profligate/strict",
            "D. an epicurean/debauched/austere"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "His actions were deemed INNOCUOUS",
        answer: "C. soothing",
        options: [
            "A. impolite",
            "B. offensive",
            "C. soothing",
            "D. appropriate"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "The girls loved the FLAMBOYANT personality of the artiste.",
        answer: "D. austere",
        options: [
            "A. ostentatious",
            "B. serious",
            "C. lavish",
            "D. austere"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "The weather is TURBULENT today",
        answer: "A. calm",
        options: [
            "A. calm",
            "B. pleasant",
            "C. motionless",
            "D. stormy"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "The needs of the ELITES constrasts with those of the _______",
        answer: "A. masses",
        options: [
            "A. masses",
            "B. oppressed",
            "C. executive",
            "D. worker"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "James HUMILITY contrasts with his sister's ___________",
        answer: "C. haughtiness",
        options: [
            "A. wickedness",
            "B. cruelty",
            "C. haughtiness",
            "D. quietness"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "We have discarded the BLUNT blades for the _________ ones.",
        answer: "C. sharp",
        options: [
            "A. japed",
            "B. rusty",
            "C. sharp",
            "D. shapened"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "The job requires the service of an EXPERIENCED programmer.",
        answer: "D. greenhorn",
        options: [
            "A. grey-beard",
            "B. old-hand",
            "C. professional",
            "D. greenhorn"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Isaac's TACITURNITY is admirable.",
        answer: "A. talkativeness",
        options: [
            "A. talkativeness",
            "B. solitude",
            "C. inactiveness",
            "D. sluggishness"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "The young girl is quite RESTIVE.",
        answer: "B. calm",
        options: [
            "A. restless",
            "B. calm",
            "C. riotous",
            "D. fast"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "Mr Saheed lives in AFFLUENCE.",
        answer: "C. penury",
        options: [
            "A. money",
            "B. wealth",
            "C. penury",
            "D. debt"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "The salad needs to be GARNISHED",
        answer: "C. watered down",
        options: [
            "A. spiced",
            "B. reduced",
            "C. watered down",
            "D. tarnished"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Hans was given a HANDSOME amount of money.",
        answer: "D. meagre",
        options: [
            "A. ugly",
            "B. stupendous",
            "C. few",
            "D. meagre"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Tom is obviously a SKIN-FLINT.",
        answer: "C. profligate",
        options: [
            "A. miser",
            "B. mendicant",
            "C. profligate",
            "D. tatterdemalion"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Jenna is FASTIDIOUS and attentive.",
        answer: "B. sloppy",
        options: [
            "A. slow",
            "B. sloppy",
            "C. swift",
            "D. dull"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Do not GLOAT over your friend's failure.",
        answer: "C. bother",
        options: [
            "A. relish",
            "B. rejoice",
            "C. bother",
            "D. schadenfreude"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "I am one of the OPULENT people in my country.",
        answer: "A. impecunious",
        options: [
            "A. impecunious",
            "B. indignant",
            "C. insolent",
            "D. indolent"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "He was a NOTORIOUS sniper during the battle.",
        answer: "C. a famous",
        options: [
            "A. a fearsome",
            "B. a popular",
            "C. a famous",
            "D. an ill-disposed"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Lola was AGITATED by the sad news of her fiance.",
        answer: "B. becalmed",
        options: [
            "A. ruffled",
            "B. becalmed",
            "C. pacifiered",
            "D. content"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "The man was condemned for his IGNOBLE role in the act.",
        answer: "D. honorable",
        options: [
            "A. unscrupulous",
            "B. nobility",
            "C. humiliating",
            "D. honorable"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "The new converts are really CONSCIENTIOUS.",
        answer: "B. carefree",
        options: [
            "A. industrious",
            "B. carefree",
            "C. responsible",
            "D. careful"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Lady Gaga is famous for her FLAMBOYANT fashion.",
        answer: "A. ascetic",
        options: [
            "A. ascetic",
            "B. holy",
            "C. righteous",
            "D. mundane"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "The teacher made a DEROGATROY comment that pissed the students off.",
        answer: "D. favorable",
        options: [
            "A. disdainful",
            "B. evocative",
            "C. placid",
            "D. favorable"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "Treasure spoke VEHEMENTLY and shook the crowd.",
        answer: "D. impassively",
        options: [
            "A. slowly",
            "B. apathetically",
            "C. grotesquely",
            "D. impassively"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Mr Sarak is very INDUSTRIOUS and lively.",
        answer: "C. slothful",
        options: [
            "A. slotful",
            "B. slutful",
            "C. slothful",
            "D. sluttish"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Mr gruff says the workers are APPROACHABLE.",
        answer: "A. ill-disposed",
        options: [
            "A. ill-disposed",
            "B. agreeable",
            "C. indisposed",
            "D. asocial"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "It is DISCOURTEOUS of him to talk at the old man in that manner.",
        answer: "A. polite",
        options: [
            "A. polite",
            "B. rude",
            "C. contemptuous",
            "D. disarming"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "John Siri was punished for his UNSCRUPULOUS attitude towards the police officer",
        answer: "C. respectful",
        options: [
            "A. arrogant",
            "B. ignoble",
            "C. respectful",
            "D. austere"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Climbing the mountain was quite an ARDUOUS task",
        answer: "A. easy",
        options: [
            "A. easy",
            "B. obvious",
            "C. unforeseen",
            "D. herculean"
        ]
    },

    {
        "question": "The nation is in a period of economic FLUX.",
        "answer": "D. stability",
        "options": [
          "A. modification",
          "B. change",
          "C. fluidity",
          "D. stability"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Yesterday, Hank was highly active but today he seems to be in an EXUBERANT spirit.",
        "answer": "A. subdued",
        "options": [
          "A. subdued",
          "B. fulsome",
          "C. lively",
          "D. bright"
        ]
      },
      
      {
        "question": "The clever lawyer exposed the facts that were OBSCURE in the case.",
        "answer": "B. obvious",
        "options": [
          "A. open",
          "B. obvious",
          "C. illustrated",
          "D. reflected"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "While Obi was HOSTILE to the quest, Nnenna remained_________.",
        "answer": "A. friendly",
        "options": [
          "A. friendly",
          "B. happy",
          "C. marvelous",
          "D. conscious"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "When Queen Esther returned to the palace, both the MAGNATE and the prince were there.",
        "answer": "D. villagers",
        "options": [
          "A. queen",
          "B. princess",
          "C. strangers",
          "D. villagers"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "The scientist made a REMARKABLE discovery.",
        "answer": "D. poor",
        "options": [
          "A. common",
          "B. rare",
          "C. significant",
          "D. poor"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "You need to get rid of SUPERFLUOUS argument.",
        "answer": "A. necessary",
        "options": [
          "A. necessary",
          "B. collective",
          "C. unimportant",
          "D. plenteous"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Many multinationals began to sell off SUBSIDIARIES.",
        "answer": "A. holdings",
        "options": [
          "A. holdings",
          "B. branches",
          "C. headquarters",
          "D. annexes"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "What they thought was a TRINKET turned out to be an INVALUABLE artefact.",
        "answer": "C. valueless",
        "options": [
          "A. valuable",
          "B. scarce",
          "C. valueless",
          "D. profitable"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "Out of anger, the lady made a very INSULTING remark.",
        "answer": "B. civil",
        "options": [
          "A. stupendous",
          "B. civil",
          "C. sophisticated",
          "D. solemn"
        ]
      },
    
      {
        "question": "At the meeting, uncle Tom made a few VULGAR statements that caused a rancor.",
        "answer": "D. polite",
        "options": [
          "A. uncouth",
          "B. curt",
          "C. acrimonious",
          "D. polite"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "The clown's OUTLANDISH stunts dazed everyone. What a superb chef d'oeuvre!",
        "answer": "C. conventional",
        "options": [
          "A. exceptional",
          "B. inferior",
          "C. conventional",
          "D. mawkish"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Speaking circumspectly, I can say Messi is actualy an ACCOMPLISHED footballer.",
        "answer": "A. untalented",
        "options": [
          "A. untalented",
          "B. unpopular",
          "C. unsuccessful",
          "D. indignant"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "Russia is one of the BELLIGERENT countries in the world.",
        "answer": "C. peaceful",
        "options": [
          "A. hostile",
          "B. bellicose",
          "C. peaceful",
          "D. parsimonious"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "Prof Khan held DISINTERESTED views about religion and politics.",
        "answer": "A. biased",
        "options": [
          "A. biased",
          "B. lackluster",
          "C. anxious",
          "D. silent"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "The athlete had grown FEEBLE due to his exposure to lethal substances.",
        "answer": "A. strong",
        "options": [
          "A. strong",
          "B. weak",
          "C. brittle",
          "D. frail"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "The artist was RENOWNED for her stunning landscapes, which captivated viewers around the world.",
        "answer": "B. infamous",
        "options": [
          "A. popular",
          "B. infamous",
          "C. ill-disposed",
          "D. notable"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "The suspect was APPREHENDED by the police after a brief chase through the city streets.",
        "answer": "D. released",
        "options": [
          "A. arrested",
          "B. misunderstood",
          "C. demystified",
          "D. released"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "The letter, signed only with AN ANONYMOUS note, contained valuable information about the upcoming event.",
        "answer": "A. a titled",
        "options": [
          "A. a titled",
          "B. a nameless",
          "C. an opaque",
          "D. a discreet"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "Despite their differences, they were able to come to AN AMICABLE agreement regarding the division of assets.",
        "answer": "B. a belligerent",
        "options": [
          "A. a peaceful",
          "B. a belligerent",
          "C. an amicabless",
          "D. a warring"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "Some children need COERCION in order to obey simple instruction rather than _________.",
        "answer": "C. persuasion",
        "options": [
          "A. convertion",
          "B. immersion",
          "C. persuasion",
          "D. transmutation"
        ]
      },

      {
        "question": "Attending morning devotion is OBLIGATORY for all the students in the hostel.",
        "answer": "A. optional",
        "options": [
          "A. optional",
          "B. mandatory",
          "C. acute",
          "D. compulsory"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Your answers are too WORDY; make them __________.",
        "answer": "D. concise",
        "options": [
          "A. verbose",
          "B. lengthy",
          "C. redundant",
          "D. concise"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "The teacher did not want to CHASTISE the student in front of the class, so she called her in privately.",
        "answer": "D. compliment",
        "options": [
          "A. complement",
          "B. rebuke",
          "C. rectify",
          "D. compliment"
        ]
      }
];
